Hello friends,
about our YouTube 4 Officer Program.
This base is starting
from the first of November. We will know the rest of the details here, like
age, qualifications, fees to join here, apart from this, what
experience is required or not required,
how will the exam be conducted and how to apply for it,
we will know everything in this video. Before moving forward, I
request you that if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel, then please
subscribe and
also press the bell icon so that all the job notifications coming in the future
reach you first. All the videos of the Bank Manpal Professional Officer
Program till date, from batch number
26 to batch number 78, will be
available in our playlist. You
can open our playlist and here
you will see ICICI Professional Officer.
You can go here and give all the information here. There is
an aptitude test here, it is an
online test,
so you have been given step by step information about this also,
all the details have been
mentioned there too, so friends, come
on our computer screen and  After going there,
you will get information about how to apply for this program,
how much will the fees be, what will be the
age qualification, we have now come to the
bank's career site and
friends, let me tell you here that this
program is II Bank Money Professional
Officer Program, okay, after doing this course,
friends, you
get ₹ 232,000 to ₹ 60,000 and apart from this, friends, you
get a certificate of Post Graduate Diploma in Banking here, which will be
very useful for you in the future,
so friends, what are the requirements for this batch number 78,
what will be the eligibility criteria, we will tell you here, so first of all, the
main important thing will be
friends, your age should be
less than 27 years, many people
also say that if it is more than 27 years, then
what will happen to them, they will not get admission here,
you cannot do this course here
because friends, the age limit that has been kept is this much  It will be
here and the
education qualification friends, here
you should have 55 plus percentage in graduation
and apart from this, if we talk
about the students here, then as a student
you get Rs. 232000 to ₹ 60000, apart from this, friends,
if we talk about the salary when
you get a job after doing this course, then your
salary is friends, you will get a salary of Rs.
5 to 55 lakhs annually and
friends,
now we will talk about the selection process in this, then the
selection process will be first, you will have an
online aptitude test, friends,
about how the online aptitude test will be conducted,
we have already made many videos here,
you can go and check it out,
I will give the link of this also in the description below, by going there
you can
click here and watch all the information videos,
then there will be round two, friends,
in round two there will be a personal interview, if
you clear the online aptitude test, then
this is a personal interview, if
you also know basic English, then you can
clear it very easily  We will take it,
okay, if we talk friends,
look here, you will definitely get the certificate of Post Graduate Diploma in
Banking for Sales and Relationship
Management
during this course, that is, there will be a 12-
month course here, what will happen during the 12-month course, we will
tell you later, here
you can earn in a way while studying, you can
also earn from ₹ 32000 to
₹ 2000000, apart from this, friends, if we talk about the
main important, then here you can
see Term One, Term Two, Term Three here, so as you join here,
what will happen to you in the first four months,
here you will have classroom training, where you will
stay in ICC MAL Academy, Bengaluru,
okay, this is residential training, so
you will have to stay there, you will get food there
and along with that, friends,
during the four months, you will get
₹ 2000000 out of ₹ 5000000 every month, as soon as four months are
over, after that Term Two will start for you,
Term Two
You will have an internship in ICICI Bank, okay, and here
you also get an opportunity to work with the experienced professionals of ICICI Bank,
where your
staff will be from 22000 to ₹ 10000 per month, you will
stay for two months, approximately
friends, here you have got ₹ 18000 here, here
you are getting ₹ 2000000,
okay, what will happen in term three,
when you do this course in term three,
you have OJD, that is, on the job
training, you will stay in ICICI Bank, and
during this OJD, you will have this OJD for about 6 months,
every month you will get a
fee of ₹ 228000 to ₹ 2000000, ₹ 2500000,
₹ 55500 is its program fee, but
friends, you are seeing here that
you are getting up to 260000, that is, the same as
your course fee
Whatever you pay, you get the same amount in return. In
a way, if we talk about
how to apply here, then to apply, friends,
you can apply by clicking on Apply Now here. Let me
tell you one more information, friends, the
fee of this program is Rs 25500 including
GST. Here, friends, the actual fee will be
2 37000 tablets. You also
get ₹1 19500. In total,
you have to pay this much amount.
By applying here, you can get yours.